scholarshipsinindia.com 2019-12-14

# Scholarships In India - Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to www.scholarshipsinindia.com is very important to us.

At www.scholarshipsinindia.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit www.scholarshipsinindia.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could includ the ability to login to some of our features, such as google groups.

We also use third party advertisements on www.scholarshipsinindia.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

In addition, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to our site. Google’s use of the Doubleclick Dart cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Visitors may opt out of the Dart cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network Advertising and Privacy Policy. Google may use interest based advertising where they recognize the types of web pages users visit across the Adsense network.This helps advertisers reach users on the basis of their interests.

**Membership Accounts**

Only we collect the Name, Email, Phone Number, city, State & Course Studying from our Membership plan. We will save our membership plan joining account holders details till the end of their date of our services.  We never sell or share the membership details ( Name, Email, Phone Number, city, State ) to other third party. Once the membership finished we will delete all the details of the particular members.
